Jennik Asare

Washington DC-Baltimore Area

jkasare525@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/jennik-asare-3102020

Summary

Information Technology Professional with 10 years' experience planning, installing, configuring, maintaining, securing, troubleshooting, and optimizing IT infrastructures to achieve high availability and performance across Windows, Linux, Mac, Virtual, and Cloud platforms. Work well independently, collaborate with teams to complete projects, and ensure effective written and verbal communication with all levels of management, teams, customers, and vendors.

Experience

Help Desk Specialist

Patriot LLC
Jul 2022 - Present (1 year 7 months)

System Administrator

NOVA Computer Solutions Nov 2021 - Jul 2022 (9 months)

🌃 IT Field Engineer

Data Business Systems
Jul 2016 - Nov 2021 (5 years 5 months)

IT Support Engineer

Federal Business Systems Jul 2015 - Jul 2016 (1 year 1 month)

🚌 IT Client Associate

Networking Technologies and Support, Inc. Aug 2014 - Jul 2015 (1 year)

Education

Capella University

Master of Science - MS, Information Systems and Technology Management 2016 - 2019

University of London

Master of Arts - MA, Education, Gender, and International Development 2008 - 2009

🏂 Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology, Kumasi

Bachelor of Science - BS, Biochemistry 1999 - 2003

Licenses & Certifications

- Accredited Project Manager International Organization for Project Management™ (IO4PM™)
- Certified Scrum Master International Scrum Institute™ (Scrum Institute)
- CompTIA Security+ CompTIA
- CompTIA Network+ CompTIA
- CompTIA IT Fundamentals+ CompTIA
- Certificate of Cloud Security Knowledge (CCSK) Cloud Security Alliance
- Certified Information Security Manager (CISM) ISACA
- MTA: Windows Server Administration Fundamentals Microsoft
- Performing a Technical Security Audit and Assessment LinkedIn
- Essential New Skills in IT Administration LinkedIn

Skills

System Administration • Information Security • Server Administration • Active Directory • Network Administration • Technical Support • Firewalls • Virtual Private Network (VPN) • Troubleshooting • Operating Systems